[Music]
I'm rames Ai and I'm a life insurance
adviser with ad Sun Life insurance for
the last 22 years basically a person who
wants to take this profession very
seriously first is he needs to have a
basic uh education and then uh a
commitment to serve the society he need
to have that commitment to uh have a
longevity in the business this is not a
getrich uh scheme where one year or 2
years he works and uh gets out of this
business if he thinks it's a long-term
if he has a long-term Vision then anyone
can come into this a person uh needs to
be uh learning on a day-to-day basis you
have to be continuously learning and uh
you have to qualify for the
international uh uh recognition that is
mdrt coot to and then you have to learn
continuously and update your knowledge
in the last 22 years there are lot of
ups and downs uh we have faced and every
person in the industry across the world
faces the same challenge one is
prospecting that is the main uh input
where uh how we can generate the
business so prospecting is one more most
people newcom especially they focus on
uh selective uh uh segment and if they
uh can't reach that they think this
industry doesn't work and then uh they
get out of that prospecting should be a
day-to-day Affair for anyone
[Music]